<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SweetPlayer</string>
    <string name="main_header">Playing Media Status</string>

    <string-array name="spinner_array">
        <item>Songs</item>
        <item>Artists</item>
        <item>Albums</item>
        <item>Genres</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="app_albums">All Albums</string>
    <string name="app_songs">All Songs</string>
    <string name="app_artists">All Artists</string>
    <string name="app_genres">All Genres</string>

    <string name="app_play_info">Use of MediaPlayer class (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/media/MediaPlayer.html)
        for playing media files(MP3 and so on), through the use of useful methods as stop/play(Pause/Play(use later) with the help
        of toggle drawable(xml)), and create(for adding audio file) and so on.
        The shuffle button would be cool if it could be used to find the current tastes of user based on the history of played audios,
        heartbeat, mood(the rate of clicking stuff(more or less excited), and use of data(A.I) to generate prefferable audio to be played
        succinctly.
    </string>

    <string name="app_content_info">Use of MediaStore class to find all media files(audio) by specifying the format we are searching and
        generating views through looping the JSON/Array results and get also the ID we are looking for and store as invisible
        information in the TextView(Tag attribute and use latter for getting the path for audio for MediaPlayer using.).</string>

    <string name="app_albums_info">Here is a list of all unique albums present in the user phone, generated into this activity, at the
    click of the button, it opens an activity with the songs that are contained in the album clicked.</string>

    <string name="app_songs_info">Here is a list of all unique songs present in the user phone, generated into this activity, clicking the
        song triggers the clickEvent with the callback to open the activity_play with the song being played.</string>

    <string name="app_genres_info">Here is a list of all unique and possible genres present in the user phone, generated into this activity,
        clicking the genre should open the songs_activity with specific if statement to find the songs with the genre we chose.</string>

    <string name="app_artists_info">Here is a list of all artists on the current phone, click an artist should open all the albums made
        by the artist chosen, and the songs afterwards.</string>

    <string name="app_song_title">The xx - I dare you.</string>

</resources>
